wvmetronews.com 2010-05-05

# West Virginia Headline News and Talk Radio

**WVMetroNews.com Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the WV MetroNews website. On some pages, you can purchase All Access, submit requests, comments, and digital files (e.g., photos, videos, and audio). The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Login Information  
Credit/Debit Card Information  
(etc.)   

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order All Access as a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address, and email address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Login Information  

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to activate the account. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

When you subscribe to All Access, you will receive a weekly text version of the Blue and Gold News. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the All Access registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by using logging into All Access and choosing to view you account details. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at info@wvmetronews.com
